# ATHIF AHAMED

athifahamed786@gmail.com +91 7904811526

https://www.linkedin.com/in/athif-ahamed 519ab1183

skype: athifahamedj@outlook.com

#### **EXECUTIVE SUMMARY**

Creative Full stack Developer offering 1+ year of experience providing high-impact web solutions for diverse industry organizations. Skilled in designing, developing and testing multiple web-based applications incorporating a range of technologies.

Aspiring to combine broad background with strong technical skills to excel as a Full stack Developer.

# **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

- HTML, CSS, Bootstrap
- Javascript, Jquery, Ajax
- PHP, MySQL
- Laravel, Codeigniter
- Wordpress
- Basic understanding of python
- C,C++,Oracle
- Photoshop and Premiere Pro

### **INTERESTS**

- Reading novels
- Writing blogs
- Solving puzzles

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## Full stack web developer

One year hands-on experience | 2019 - 2020

- Developed responsive websites from front to backend using PHP, JavaScript, Jquery, Ajax, Bootstrap, HTML and CSS with MySQL database.
- Worked on PHP frameworks such as Laravel and Codeigniter
- Developed dynamic websites for Ecommerce, POS, also worked on Wordpress sites including payment gateway such as paytm, paypal etc.
- Designed and developed user friendly websites including testing and bug fixings that improved web functionality and responsiveness.

### **GBS Systems and Services**

PHP developer | 31/03/2021 - 30/09/2021

• Worked as a Full stack Web developer in POS softwares

# Softlogic academy

Web technologies | 19/01/2019 - 21/04/2019

 Certified course and trained on languages such as HTML, CSS, Javascript and PHP.

# **EDUCATION HIGHLIGHTS**

#### Aalim muhammed salegh college of engineering

Electronics and communication | 2015 - 2019

• CGPA - 6.7/10

# Sri venkateshwara matric. higher sec school, Chennai.

Higher Secondary | 2015

• 70.50%

# Saraswathi vidyalaya matric. higher sec school, Muthupet. SSLC | 2013

• 94%

# LANGUAGES SPOKEN

Tamil, English and Hindi